Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1875-2014 and undated; 5
  - Advertising--Agencies--MacDuff, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Advertising--Agencies--McCabe, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Ogilvy, 1989-1997; 2 folders (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Omnicom-Publicis merger, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Publicis, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Rawle Murdy, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Saatchi Saatchi, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Stan Frieberg, 1969-1989 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Swankt's, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--TBWA, circa 1992 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--The Syndicate, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Young Rubicam, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Advertising--Articles about the advertising industry, 1977-2001 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Advertising--"Best of" lists, 1992-1997 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Advertising--History/Nostalgia, 1985-1993; 3 folders (Box 30, Folder 17-19)
  - Advertising--History/Nostalgia, 1990-2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Advertising--Icons, 2000-2003; 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Advertising--Miscellaneous ads, old ads, 1920s-2010; 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
  - Advertising--Music and advertising, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Advertising--Postcards/Go Cards/Direct mail, undated, 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
  - Advertising--Print advertising innovations, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Advertising--Trends--Amateurs/DIY, 1987-1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Advertising--Trends--CD-ROM's, 2002-2004 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Advertising--Trends--Celebrity endorsements, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Advertising--Trends--Clutter, 1986-1989 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Advertising--Trends--Co-branding/Joint promotion, 1988-1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Advertising--Trends--Coupons and fraud, 1978-2005 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Advertising--Trends--"Dudes", 1991-1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Advertising--Trends--Infomercials, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Advertising--Trends--Self-Referential/Ad-on-ad/Parody, 1988-1998 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Advertising--Trends--Stealth brand parentage, name changes, 1994-1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - American Express, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - AOL (America Online), undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Arthur DeMoss Foundation (abortion), 1991-1995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Aunt Jemima, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Automobiles, 1966-2004; 4 folders (Box 32, Folder 11-14)
  - Automobiles--Amati, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Automobiles--Edsel, circa 1960-1998 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Automobiles--Electric, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Automobiles--Kaiser, Henry J., 1970 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Automobiles--Lexus, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Automobiles--Saturn, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Baseball, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Baseball--Mark McGuire 62 home run edition, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Beer, 1970-1996; 2 folders (Box 32, Folder 23-24)
  - Beer--Anheuser-Busch, 1978-1990 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Beer--Miller history, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Beer--Miller Time campaign, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Beer--Molson, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - British Airways--Concorde Vacations, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Burma Shave, 1994-1997 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Buster Brown, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Campbell Soup, 1983-1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Candy, 1984-1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Chiquita Banana jingle, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cigarettes, 1988-1997; 4 folders (Box 33, Folder 7-10)
  - Cigarettes--Benson Hedges, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Cigarettes--Camel, 1991-1999; 3 folders (Box 33, Folder 12-14)
  - Cigarettes--Chesterfield, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Cigarettes--Cigarette Century (John A. Meyer), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Cigarettes--Kool, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Cigarettes--Marlboro, 1987-1996; 2 folders (Box 33, Folder 18-19)
  - Cigarettes--Tobacco Settlement, 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Cigarettes--Winston, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Clothing--Abercrombie Fitch, 1996-1999 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Clothing--Calvin Klein, 1992-1999; 4 folders (Box 34, Folder 2-5)
  - Clothing--Calvin Klein--Woody Harrelson mock billboard from film Cowboy Way, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Coca-Cola, 1933-2011; 3 folders (Box 34, Folder 7-9)
  - Coca-Cola--Robert Woodruff special, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Coffee, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Coffee--Maxwell House Passover Haggadah (English and Hebrew), 2011 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Coffee--Postum, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Coffee--Taster's Choice "Couple" campaign, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Colgate: 200 Years, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Collector cards, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Contests, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Cosmetics, 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Cracker Jack, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Cream of Wheat 1899-1990s ads (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Diet Coke, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Energizer batteries, 1991-1998 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Enron: A Guide to the Enron Brand, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Eziba (retailer), 2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Gay/Lesbian anti-violence, 1999-2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Geico, 2013-2014 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Jack in the Box, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - JetBlue, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Jingles and music, 1988-1999; 2 folders (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
  - Kellogg's, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Levi Strauss, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - LGBT--Advertising and coverage, 1984-2003; 2 folders (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
  - LGBT--Advertising and coverage, 1984-2003; 2 folders (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - LGBT--Advocacy, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - LGBT--Bullying, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - LGBT--Market studies, 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - LGBT--Market studies, 2001-2003; 2 folders (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - Liquor, 1988-1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Liquor--Absolut Vodka, 1988-2003; 3 folders (Box 37, Folder 4-6)
  - Liquor--Canadian Club, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Liquor--Chivas Regal, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Liquor--Tanqueray, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Liquor--Vodka, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Listerine, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Magazines, circa 1970-1986 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Magazines--Cosmo Girl, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Magazines--Cosmopolitan--Cosmo men including Burt Reynolds, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Magazines--Life, 1936-2009; 2 folders (Box 37, Folder 15-16)
  - Magazines--Look, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Magazines--New Yorker, 1992-1998 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Magazines--Saturday Evening Post, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Magazines--Woman's Day covers, undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Male models/celebrities, 1989-1996 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Maytag Repairman 35th annniversary, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - McDonald's Back to Bedrock, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Michael Jackson, undated (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Milk campaigns, 1995-1998 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Miss Subway, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Mobil at 125, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Movies, 1984-1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Movies--A Christmas Story, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Movies--And the Band Played On, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Movies--Apatow's Undeclared, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Movies--Batman Forever, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Movies--Casablanca, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Movies--Castro's Movie Palace, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Movies--Cocktail, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Movies--Fire Island, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Movies--Harry Potter, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Movies--Jerry Maguire, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Movies--Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Movies--Kung Fu Panda 2, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Movies--Lord of the Rings, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Movies--Miracle on 34th Street, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Movies--Miscellaneous, 1979-2005; 2 folders (Box 38, Folder 18-19)
  - Movies--Moviegoer magazine, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Movies--Prêt-á-porter, undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Movies--Purple Rose of Cairo, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Movies--September credits list, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Movies--Shrek pop-up booklet, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Movies--Star Wars, 1979-1999; 3 folders (Box 38, Folder 25-27)
  - Movies--The Devil's Own, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Movies--The Incredibles, undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Movies--The Usual Suspects production notes, undated (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Movies--Titanic, 1992-1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Movies--Twentieth Century Fox, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Moxie soda, 1967-1985 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Museum of Beverage Containers, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Nabisco 200th anniversary, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - National Fluid Milk Processors, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - New York Times centennial, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - News stars sell out, 1990-1999 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper industry--Articles about, 1976-2005 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Norelco, 1976-1994 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - NYNEX, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - O.J. Simpson, 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Outdoor advertising, 1934-2002; 2 folders (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
  - Packaging, 1988-2002 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Pastis restaurant (New York), undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Peanuts cartoon, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Pedometers, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Pepsi jingles and songs, 1940-1993 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Piggly Wiggly, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Planter's Mr. Peanut, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Politics--Obamacare/Papa John's/Macy's, etc., 2012-2013 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Politics--Politicians in ads, 1996-1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Politics--Post-election, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Pop Rocks/Space Dust, circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Procter Gamble, 1994-1996 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Prodigy, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Public relations, 1949-1995 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Radio, 1962-2000; 2 folders (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
  - Rely tampons--Box and article, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Research, focus groups, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Restaurants, cafeterias, automats, 1984-1985 and undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Retailers, 1875-1993 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - S.C. Johnson--Raid, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Shoes, footwear, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Snapple, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Social media--Articles about, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Southland/7-Eleven, 1927-1997 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Sports--Century 21 Turn Ahead the Clock, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Sports marketing--Baltimore Orioles at Camden Yards, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Television--3D, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Television--ABC, 1990-1999 and undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Television--Adland proposal, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Television--American Idol, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Television--Amos n Andy, 1982-1997 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Television--Articles about, 1978-2007 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Television--Baywatch, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Television--Buffy the Vampire Slayer, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Television--CBS, 1977-1983 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Television--CBS Marketalk program development special edition, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Television--Channel One, 1989-1997 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Television--Charmed, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Television--Cheers, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Television--Commercials, 1983-1998 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Television--Dawson's Creek, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Television--Ellen DeGeneres, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Television--Felicity, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Television--Footballers' Wives (BBC) commemorative nail file, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Television--Fox/FX, 1994-2005 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Television--Gay networks, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Television--Hyperion Bay, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Television--Mad Men, 2007-2011; 4 folders (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - Television--Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Television--Miscellaneous, 1975-2006; 3 folders (Box 42, Folder 6-8)
  - Television--MTM Entertainment stock prospetus, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Television--MTV Jukka Brothers, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Television--NBC, 1987-2005 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Television--NBC--Circle of Friends, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Television--NBC--Saturday Night Live, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Television--Party of Five, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Television--Queer as Folk, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Television--Queer Eye for the Straight Guy, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 42, Folder 16-17)
  - Television--Queer Eye for the Straight Guy, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Television--Roswell, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Television--Seinfeld, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Television--Star Trek, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Television--Supernatural, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Television--That 70s Show, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Television--The Beauty Show, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Television--The O.C., 2007 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Television--The Simpsons, 1994-1998 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Television--The WB, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
  - Television--Time Warner Cable News, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Television--Turner Classic Movies (TCM), 2008-2011 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Television--TV Land: More than 2000 Years of Television, 1999; 2 folders (Box 43, Folder 14-15)
  - Television--Twenty Four, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Television--USA Today, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Television--VH1 Pop-Up Video, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Television--Viacom Logo (Gay television network) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - The 1950s, 2001-2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Theater, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Theater--Catch Me If You Can, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Theater--Music, 1980-1998 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Forest Service--Smokey Bear: The First 50 Years, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service--Elvis stamp, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Wendy's, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Wine, champagne, 1962-1969 and undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Trade Contacts, undated, 6
  - Contact files, Rolodex, business cards, etc. (unsorted), undated (Box 45)
  - Contact files, Rolodex, business cards, etc. (unsorted), undated (Box 46)
- Writings File, 1969-2014 and undated; 7
  - 1969-2014, 1
    - 1969-1996--Coca-Cola, 3 folders (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
    - 1978 March 14--And Now a Word About Sponsors (Elliott's first article on advertising) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1981-2007--Miscellaneous articles (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - 1991 August 12--Public service campaigns (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - 1991 October 2--J. Walter Thompson (JWT) (Box 47, Folder 6a)
    - 1991-2013--ANA (Association of National Advertisers) (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - 1991-2014--AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies), 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - 1992-2001--Pepsi, 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
    - 1994-1996--LGBT advertising, 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 5-6)
    - 1999-2001--LGBT advertising, 2 folders (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - 1994-2007--Super Bowl, 5 folders (Box 49, Folder 3-7)
    - 1996 April 19--Multi-racial ads (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - 1997 August 11--Betty Crocker (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - 1998 March 13--VW Beetle (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - 1998 August 3--Apple "Think Different" (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - 2000 June 2--Luck as a selling tool (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - 2001--Jeep (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - 2000 May 10--Viracept (HIV/AIDS), 2001 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - 2001 July 9--Gays and sports (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - 2002--LGBT--Rosie O'Donnell (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - 2002-2005--Mega-Features (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - 2003--Bravo TV: Boy Meets Boy (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - 2004--Gay celebrity endorsements (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - 2004--Pier One/LGBT marketing (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - 2005-2006--TV Upfronts, 2 folders (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
    - 2005 February 28--TCM/Product placement in the movies (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - 2005 april 4--Boutique agencies (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - 2005 September 26--Movies: Prize Winner of Defiance Ohio (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - 2005 December 12--Alka-Seltzer (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - 2006 April 5--Polaroid (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - 2006 June 19--Alka-Seltzer (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - 2006 September 6--Bud TV (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - 2006 September 7--Wal-Mart agency review (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - 2006 September 13--Wacky job titles (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - 2006 September 28--Bromo-Seltzer (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - 2006 October 26--Wal-Mart agency review (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - 2006 December 8--Wal-Mart/Julie Roehm (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - 2006 December 9,15--Wal-Mart, 2 folders (Box 51, Folder 12-13)
  - 2007, 2
    - 1/13--Wal-Mart, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - 1/18-22--Orville Redenbacher, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 1a)
    - 1/22--Plavix, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - 3/21--ANA Conference, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - 3/28--Martin Sorrell, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 3/30--Uncle Ben's, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - 3/30--Wal-Mart, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - 4/9--MDC Partners, 2007; 2 folders (Box 52, Folder 7-8)
    - 4/18--Hyundai, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - 4/24--Volvo, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - 4/25--Automobiles/Audi, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - 4/27--Absoult Vodka, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 5/14--TV Upfronts, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 5/15--NBC Upfront, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 5/16--ABC Upfront, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 5/17--TV Upfronts, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 5/18--CW/Fox Upfront, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 5/21--TV Upfronts, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 5/22--CW Now, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 6/11--High school sports, 2007; 2 folders (Box 53, Folder 9-10)
    - 6/20--BP oil slick, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 6/26-27--Robert Coen/Advertising outlook, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 7/6--Dance in advertisements, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 8/16--Cigarettes: Camel #9, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 8/27--Princess Diana 10th anniversary, 2007; 2 folders (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
    - 9/5--Porsche, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - 9/17--Halloween, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 9/19--Lending Tree, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - 9/20--Kid Nation, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - 9/24--Brooklyn Advertising High School, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - 9/28--Chevron "Human Energy" campaign, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - 10/2--Jingles, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - 10/7--Financial sector advertising, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - 10/9--Stealth Christmas, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - 10/22--CNN, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - 10/26-31--iPod Touch, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - 10/29--Halloween, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - 10/30-31--Super Bowl, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - 11/1--Wal-Mart holiday ads, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - 11/2--Ellen DeGeneres for Toyota, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - 11/13--Reebok "Framed", 2007 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - 11/20--Copycat/imitative ad campaigns, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - 11/23--American Life TV, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - 11/26--Rolling Stone/R.J. Reynolds/Camel, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - 11/29--R.J. Reynolds and print ads, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - 11/30--WNBC/Bacardi, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 12/3-4--UBS Media Conference/Industry forecasts, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - 12/4-5--R.J. Reynolds sued, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - 12/5--UBS: Advertising Revenue/Brian Wieser, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 12/6--McDonald's and Florida "Report Card" promotion, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 12/10--The 1960s in advertising, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - 12/17--Budweiser, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Chief Digital Officers, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - FedEx, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Garmin, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - High School Musical 2, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Planters, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Salesgenie.com, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Starbucks, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Bridgestone, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Virgin Mobile "You Rule" NYC campaign, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - When Agencies Say No, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - 2008, 3
    - 1/10--GSN (Game Show Network) Black White Overnight, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - 1/16--NBC, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - 1/18--McDonald's/Florida schools follow-up, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - 1/22--Anheuser-Busch Super Bowl, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 1/22--Club Med, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - 1/22--Sizzler, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - 1/24-25--AAAA/Nancy Hill, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - 1/28--Recessions, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - 2/4--Super Bowl review, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - 2/5--Super Bowl follow-up, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - 2/6--IAG Research, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - 2/6--Salesgenie.com, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - 2/15--Camel #9 cigarettes, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - 2/19--J.C. Penney, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - 2/20--Super Bowl, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - 2/20--NBC, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - 2/26--Oscars, 2008; 2 folders (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
    - 3/5--Alka-Seltzer "Speedy", 2008 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 3/12--Abercrombie Fitch/National Children's Hospital, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 3/17--Sex the City series, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - 3/20--Stephen Colbert/Frito-Lay, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - 3/21--Hincapie Barkley, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - 3/26--Hal Riney, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - 3/31--Emsense, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - 4/2--NBC/Liberty Mutual sponsorhip, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 4/3--NBS upfront, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 4/9--Bleeping vulgarity, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 4/11--Ads and magazines, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - 4/16--Human Rights Commission (Advertising industry hiring), 2008 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 4/28-5/1--AAAA conference, 2008; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
    - 5/12--Telemundo upfront, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - 5/12--Upfronts, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - 5/13--ABC, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - 5/13--NBC/General Motors, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - 5/14--Upfronts, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - 5/15--Upfronts, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 5/19--Upfronts, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 5/21--Live ads, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 5/23--Disney tourism, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 5/29--I Love New York, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - 5/30--TV Upfronts, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - 6/11--Upfronts, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - 6/12--Mojo HD/Dos Equis, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - 6/16--Backchannel, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - 6/18--Family Guy, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - 6/18--Yankelovich: Traditional media, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - 6/23--Real Men and Women of Madison Avenue, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - 6/23--Real Men and Women of Madison Avenue, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - 6/24--Alcohol advertising, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 6/25--Keller Fay/Word of mouth, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - 6/26--Howard Beale (character in film Network), 2008 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 7--Olympics, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 7/2--G23/Women's Economy, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 7/7--Pod-Busters, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - 7/8-9--Robert Coen on ad spending, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - 7/14--Sears, J.C. Penney back-to-school, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 7/14--Wal-Mart "Momtourage", 2008 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - 8/9--NBC Olympics, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 8/11--Automobile advertising, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - 8/11--John McCain Olympics spot, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 8/11--SpotCo, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - 8/13--International Harvester, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 8/15--Out-of-home, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 8)